Finding Aid for the Walter E. Bennett Photographic Collection LSC.0686
UCLA Library Special Collections
Walter E. Bennett photographic collection
1937-1983
1952-1982
UCLA Library Special Collections
Bennett, Walter E. (Walter Edward)
LSC.0686
4.0 Linear Feet (8 boxes and 1 oversize box)
Walter E. Bennett (1921-1995) was the first salaried photographer for Time, where he worked from 1952 to 1982. The collection consists of photographic materials such as prints, negatives and slides. It also includes miscellaneous manuscripts and ephemera related to Bennett's life and career.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
PORTIONS OF THIS COLLECTION HAVE BEEN DIGITIZED. See the Existence and Location of Copies note for the link to the digitized materials.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digitized materials are available electronically at https://digital.library.ucla.edu/catalog/m8f11000zz-89112.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Lisa Bennett, 2005.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9953735153606533
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Miscellaneous, 1937-1982
Prints, 1955-1984
Slides, 1952-1981
Loose negatives, 1953-1982
Batched negatives, 1953-1967
Biography/History
Walter Edward Bennett was born on August 16, 1921 in the London suburb of Hornsey, England. He attended John C. Fremont High School in Los Angeles, where he was first exposed to photography through a vocational training class. On November 11, 1942 Bennett joined the Army as a camera man and photo lab tech. He was honorably discharged on January 3, 1946 from the 18th Reinforcement Battalion. Upon returning to Los Angeles, Bennett became a life guard at Hermosa Beach. In 1952, Bennett was hired by Time and became the first-ever salaried photographer at the magazine. For the next 30 years, Bennett worked primarily in Washington D.C. where he photographed presidents, politicians, foreign dignitaries, events, and notable personalities. During this time, Bennett was sent on numerous assignments to photograph presidents during visits of state. Bennett's proximity and longevity in the press arena of Washington D.C. led to his befriending a number of politicians, such as Lyndon B. Johnson, Hubert Humphrey and members of the Kennedy family. Bennett retired in 1982 and died on April 29, 1995.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of photographic materials such as prints, negatives and slides taken by Walter E. Bennett. It also includes miscellaneous manuscripts and ephemera related to Bennett's life and career, such as scrapbooks, clippings, and letters. Bennett's photography documents public figures in Washington D.C., from Presidents Eisenhower through Reagan. The images include portraits of notable politicians and celebrities, shots of anti-Vietnam and Civil Rights protests and marches, foreign travels and campaign trails of presidents, political party conventions, and The Beatles' 1964 and 1966 Washington D.C. concerts and press conferences. Many of the images are unpublished.
News photographs.; News photographers -- Archives.; Bennett, Walter E. (Walter Edward)
- Series 1: Miscellaneous, 1937-1982; 0.5 box, 0.5 oversize box.
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of miscellaneous items related to the life and career of Walter E. Bennett. Materials include a scrapbook that highlights Bennett's accomplishments and career, clippings, letters, and other assorted materials. Materials are arranged in chronological order.
  - Scrapbook., [3 folders].
    Picture book comprised of clippings, photographic prints, and letters related to the life and career of Walter Bennett.
    - First 19 pages of scrapbook., ca. 1937 - 1947. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Second 19 pages of scrapbook., ca. 1947 - 1956. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Last 15 pages of scrapbook., ca. 1956 - 1982. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous letters., 1961 December 18. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Letters from unidentified Vice President and Rep. Carl Vinson (Georgia) to Bennett.
  - Assorted clippings., 1966 - 1980. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Clippings include some of Bennett's published photos in Time Magazine, industry newsletters, and newspaper clippings (see Box 2 for oversize materials).
  - Letters during surgery., 1967 November 28. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Letters from Vice President Hubert Humphrey and President Lyndon Johnson wishing Bennett a speedy recovery from surgery.
  - Robert Kennedy funeral materials., 1968. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Includes telegram press invitation hymn book.
  - Assorted invitations., 1968 - 1969. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Press invitations addressed to Bennett from White House and Information Officers from Pakistan and India.
  - Awards and certificates., 1968, 1978. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Includes certificate of membership to The Explorer's Club and a honorable mention ribbon.
  - Letter from Edward Kennedy., 1969 January 9. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Letter from Edward Kennedy, includes signed Time Magazine cover.
  - Letters of condolence., 1979 February 8, 9. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Letters from Senator Howard H. Baker Jr. and Vice President Walter F. Mondale offering Bennett condolences after his mother's death.
  - Anniversary letters., 1982 January. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Letters from colleagues and comrades congratulating Bennett on his 30 years at Time Magazine.
  - Oversize clippings., 1976 May 23. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Special issue of the Washington Post Potomac section on Washington D.C. photography. Includes shots by Walter Bennett.
- Series 2: Prints, 1955-1984; 0.5 box, 0.5 oversize box.
  This series consists of photographic prints by Walter E. Bennett. Prints include: Presidents Eisenhower through Reagan, The Beatles, and miscellaneous oversize photos. Arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
  - The Beatles., 1964 February 13 and 1966 August 17. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    8 x 10" black and white proof sheets and 4.5 x 6" prints of Beatles' Washington D.C. concerts and press conferences.
  - Bennett, Walter., [2 folders].
    - Color and black and white prints of Bennett throughout his photo career., ca. 1960 - 1980.; Various sizes. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Black and white prints of Bennett and friends on vacation., 1965.; Various sizes. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Carter, Jimmy., ca. 1977.; Various sizes. Color and black and white prints. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., ca. 1955. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Various sizes. Black and white prints of portraits, wife Mamie, inauguration, and miscellaneous shots (see also Box 2, folder 2 for oversize prints).
  - Ford, Gerald., ca. 1974 - 1977. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    8 x 10" black and white proof sheets of Ford playing golf with Jack Nicklaus and others.
  - Humphrey, Hubert., ca. 1965 -1969. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    8 x 10" black and white proof sheet of portraits of Humphrey and shots during speech.
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., ca.1963 -1969. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    8 x 10" black and white prints and proof sheet of Johnson signing bill, speaking, and greeting crowd.
  - Kennedy, John F., ca. 1962. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    4.5 x 6" black and white prints of Kennedy with Eisenhower, his brother Robert, at a press conference, and shots of wife Jackie.
  - Kennedy, Robert., 1960 June - 1963 June. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    8 x 10" black and white proof sheets of Kennedy with family, at work, and portraits of wife Ethel.
  - McCarthy, Joseph., ca. 1955. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    8 x 10" black and white prints of portrait and shots at rally. Includes 10 x 14" cartoon print of McCarthy and Eisenhower.
  - Nixon, Richard., ca. 1960-1970. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    8 x 10" black and white proof sheets of Nixon during early campaign trail and as President at a ball.
  - Ray, James Earl., 1977 June. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    8 x 10" black and white proof sheets of Martin Luther King assassin and attorney at House Select Committee on Assassinations
  - Reagan, Ronald., ca. 1982. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    8 x 10" color print of Reagan and Bennett's daughter. Signed.
  - Times Magazine staff., ca. 1970 -1980. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Various sizes. Color and black and white prints of Bennett with Times Magazine photo staff.
  - Unidentified., ca. 1960 - 1984. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Various sizes. Color and black and white prints and proof sheets of unidentified subjects. 1 print signed.
  - Miscellaneous oversize., ca. 1955 - 1972.; 11 x 13" black and white prints. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Includes shots of John F. Kennedy, Dwight Eisenhower, Gerald Ford, and the Poor People's March.
- Series 3: Slides, 1952-1981; 3.5 boxes.
  This series consists of photographic slides by Walter E. Bennett. Slides include: Presidents Eisenhower through Reagan, various politicians, foreign dignitaries, protests, and marches. Arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
  - Abel, I.W., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alphano, Mdme., 1963 November.; Color portraits. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Arlington National Cemetery funeral., ca. 1970. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Color shots of funeral; deceased unknown.
  - Bennett, Walter., ca. 1952-1978. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Black and white and color shots of Bennett taking photos and posing with celebrities, politicians, and friends.
  - Betbeze/Fox, Yolande., ca. 1975.; Color portraits. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Buchanon, Pat., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bullfight., ca. 1970. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Color shots of a bullfight.
  - Carter, Jimmy., 1977 - 1981. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Color and black and white shots of Carter throughout his presidency. Includes shots of wife Rosalyn, meeting dignitaries, traveling, press conferences, and inauguration.
    - President Jimmy Carter and daughter Amy Carter watch First Lady Rosalynn Carter's flight depart for her South American tour June 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - President Jimmy Carter and Senator Ted Kennedy ca. 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - President Jimmy Carter speaks at the White House ca. 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - President Jimmy Carter speaks to a crowd in New York City during a 1978 campaign endorsment for Democrats Hugh Carey and Mario Cuomo 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chesser, Al H., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Church of Redeemer., 1960 November. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    4 x 5" color shots of interior and exterior of Episcopal church in Baltimore, Maryland.
  - Congress Hearings on Energy., ca. 1970. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Color shots of Congressional hearings.
  - Democratic Convention 1976., 1976 July. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Color shots of convention. Includes shots of Jimmy Carter, Walter Mondale, and other speakers.
  - Dennis, C.L., ca. 1965.; Color portraits. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dirksen, Everett., 1964. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Color shots of Dirksen speaking at 1964 GOP convention
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1953 - 1969 March 31, April 2. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Color shots of Eisenhower speaking, with Nikita Khrushchev, and funeral in Washington D.C. and Abilene, Kansas.
    - President Dwight Eisenhower July 1964 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - President Dwight Eisenhower and Premier of the Soviet Union Nikita Khrushchev watch Khrushchev's wife Nina Petrovna exit car during Khrushchev's September 1959 visit to Washington D.C. September 1959 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Ford, Gerald., ca. 1974-1977. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Color shots of Ford at press conference, meeting with Anwar Sadat, and with wife Betty.
    - President Gerald Ford and Egyptian President Anwar Sadat October 26, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Glenn, John., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Goldwater, Barry., 1964 July. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Color shots from 1964 Republican Convention. Includes shots of William Miller and wife, Peggy.
  - Habib, Philip., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Humphrey, Hubert., ca.1965-1970. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Color portraits and shots from campaign trail and speaking engagements.
  - Japan., ca. 1975. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Color shots from trip to Japan. Includes pictures of geisha and landmarks.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird., 1967. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Color shots from Johnson's trip to Thailand.
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., ca. 1963-1973. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Color and black and white shots of Johnson throughout his presidency. Includes shots of various travels, press conferences, campaigns, portraits, inauguration, in church during Pope Paul's visit with Jackie Kennedy, and funeral.
    - President Johnson covers his ears during a campaign parade in California October 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - President Lyndon B. Johnson rides a horse during a 1964 presidential campaign event September, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - President Lyndon B. Johnson speaks at a White House press conference April 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - President Lyndon Johnson and Attorney General Robert F. Kennedy greet a crowd during Kennedy's senatorial campaign parade through Brooklyn, New York 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy Center opening., 1971 September. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Color shots from opening night at Kennedy center.
  - Kennedy, John F. and Jackie., 1961 July, 1963 January. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Color and black and white shots. Includes shots of trip to Mt. Vernon with Muhammad Ayub Khan and wife, and at Mona Lisa press conference.
  - Kennedy, Robert., 1968 June 8. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Color and black and white shots of family portrait, solo portrait, and shots from funeral.
    - Attorney General Robert Kennedy with his wife, Ethel Kennedy, and six children (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - King, Coretta Scott., ca. 1968.; Color shots. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kissinger, Henry., ca. 1970. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Color shots of Kissinger with Dean Rusk at Congressional hearing.
    - Henry Kissinger with South Vietnamese Vice Premier Nguyen Cao Ky and Ellsworth Bunker in Saigon ca. 1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kissinger, Nancy., ca. 1970. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Color shots with Jihan Sadat.
  - Kubitschek, Juscelino., 1956 January 6.; Color portraits. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lane, Bert., ca. 1975. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Color portraits with wife.
  - Love, Governor John Arthur (Colorado)., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - May Day protest., 1971 May 3. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Color shots from protest in Washington D.C.
    - Anti-war demonstrators attend the 1971 May Day Protest in Washington D.C. May 3, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Anti-war demonstrators sit on the steps of the Capital building during the 1971 May Day Protest in Washington D.C. May 3, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - McCarthy, Joseph., ca. 1957. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Color shots from Congressional hearing.
  - Miller, Arnold., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mondale, Walter., ca. 1977. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Color shots of Mondale and unidentified others gardening.
  - Mother Teresa., 1981 June.; Color portraits. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Nader, Ralph., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Navy Seal training., 1963 February. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Color shots of Navy Seals in training.
  - Nixon, Richard., 1969-1975.; [2 folders]. (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
    Color and black and white shots of Nixon throughout his presidency. Includes shots of various travels, press conferences, speeches, campaigns, meeting dignitaries, inauguration, parades, and other social functions.
    - President Richard Nixon and First Lady Patricia Nixon with President of the Philippines Ferdinand Marcos and First Lady Imelda Marcos, during a visit to the Philippines July 27, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Nixon holds President Marcos's son, Ferdinand Marcos, Jr., while dressed in a traditional Filipino shirt (barong tagalog).
    - President Richard Nixon speaks to American troops in Di~ An, Vietnam July 30, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - President Richard Nixon waves to the crowd during a 1969 parade through West Berlin, Germany February 27, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Title: Vice President Richard Nixon gives a speech during his 1960 presidential campaign September 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - President Richard Nixon speaks to a crowd during his 1968 incumbent presidential campaign 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - President Richard Nixon speaks to a crowd during his 1968 incumbent presidential campaign 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Opening of Congress., 1977. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Color shots of floor of Congress during opening ceremony.
  - Panama., 1963 February. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Color shots of visit to Panama.
  - Poor People's March., 1968 August. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Color shots of the Resurrection City civil rights protest.
  - Presidential Seal., 1961.; 4 x 5" color transparencies of the Presidential Seal. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Reagan, Ronald., ca. 1981-1989. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Color shots of Reagan on vacation, at a parade, and speaking during press conference.
    - President Ronald Reagan ca. 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - President Ronald Reagan and First Lady Nancy Reagan at a beach ca. 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - President Ronald Reagan and First Lady Nancy Reagan at Presidential Inauguartion, 1981 January 20, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Republican Convention 1976., 1976 August 16-19. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Color shots of convention crowd and Betty Ford accepting cheers.
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor., ca. 1950s.; Black and white portraits. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Scharp, Governor., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Schneiker, Senator., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Scott, Senator Hugh., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Shanker, Albert., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Tony., 1962 October 13. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Black and white shot of Time Magazine cover.
  - Sorenson, Theodore., 1961 June.; Color portraits. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Teotihuacan., 1963 September. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Color shots from of visit to Teotihuacan.
  - Thatcher, Margaret., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified., ca. 1963-1970. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Color shots of unidentified subjects and locations/happenings. Includes portraits, shots of various travels, candlelight vigil, duck hunt, protest, and baptism. Also includes 2 x 2" color transparencies of cowboys shooting craps.
    - Female protestor campaigns against the Equal Rights Amendment ca. 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Vietnam War Out Now Demonstration., 1971 April 24. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Color shots of crowd at protest.
    - Costumed anti-war demonstrators at the 1971 Vietnam War Out Now protest, Washington D.C. April 24, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Demonstrators gather in front of Capital building for the 1971 Vietnam War Out Now protest in Washington D.C. April 24, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - White House., 1962 January, 1963 April. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Color shots of Red Room, Green Room, Diplomatic Room, and exterior.
  - Warren, Earl., 1974 July. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Color shots from funeral outside of Supreme Court.
  - Sunset in Washington D.C., ca. 1970. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Color shots of Washington Monument at sunset.
  - Woodcock, Leonard., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Wurf, Jerry., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Zumwalt, Admiral Elmo Russell., ca. 1970.; Color portraits. (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Series 4: Loose negatives, 1953-1982; 0.5 box.
  This series consists of negatives by Walter E. Bennett that were loosely stored and organized in a folder. Negatives include: Presidents Truman through Reagan, various politicians, foreign dignitaries, and The Beatles. Arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
  - Baker, Bobby., 1964 February. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Black and white shots of Baker and others during congressional hearings.
  - The Beatles., 1966 August 17. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Black and white shots of the band at Washington D.C. concert and press conference.
    - Audience during Beatles August 15, 1966 Washington D.C. performance at D.C. Stadium August,15 1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - The Beatles are greeted by the press while exiting airplane in Washington D.C. during 1966 American tour (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - The Beatles at a press conference in Washington D.C. during 1966 American tour August 1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - The Beatles at a press conference in Washington D.C. during 1966 American tour August 1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Bennett, Walter., ca. 1960. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    2.5 x 2.5" black and white shots of Bennett.
  - Bullfight., ca. 1970.; 4 x 5" color shots of a bullfight. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Bundy, William., 1964 March.; Black and white portraits. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Burger, Chief Justice Warren., 1964 May.; Black and white portraits. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Carter, Jimmy., ca. 1977-1981. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    4 x 5" and 2.5 x 2.5" color shots of Carter and wife, Rosalyn.
  - Dulles, John Foster., ca. 1955. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    2.5 x 2.5" black and white shots of Dulles at press conference and with former Secretary of State Dean Acheson.
  - Eisenhower, Dwight., ca. 1953-1964. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Black and white shots of Eisenhower throughout presidency. Includes 4 x 5" black and white shot of inauguration speech.
    - President Dwight D. Eisenhower fishing ca.1953-1960 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - President Dwight D. Eisenhower greets crowd during speech ca. 1953-1960 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - President Dwight D. Eisenhower playing golf ca. 1953-1960 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Title: President Eisenhower shields himself from confetti during a parade ca.1953-1960 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Flood, Daniel., 1964 April.; Black and white portraits. (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - President John F. Kennedy with First Lady Jacqueline Kennedy ca. 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Ford, Gerald., 1959-1977. (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Black and white portraits and shots of Ford speaking and playing golf.
    - Congressman Gerald Ford in his office ca. 1959 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - President Gerald Ford golfing with golf professional Jack Nicklaus ca. 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Humphrey, Hubert., ca.1965-1970. (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Black and white portraits and shots of Humphrey speaking in front of Johnson image backdrop. Includes 4 x 5" shot of same image.
  - Johnson, Lyndon., ca. 1960-1969. (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Black and white shots of Johnson throughout political career. Includes 4 x 5" color shots.
  - Kefauver, Estes., ca. 1955-1960. (Box 6, Folder 29)
    2.5 x 2.5" black and white shots of the Senator with child.
  - Kennedy, John F., ca. 1955-1963. (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Black and white shots of Kennedy throughout political career. Includes shots with Eisenhower, speaking, with brother Robert, and with wife Jackie.
    - President John F. Kennedy answers questions during a White House press conference ca. 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - President John F. Kennedy with brother and Attorney General Robert F. Kennedy ca. 1961 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Senator John F. Kennedy ca. 1953-1960 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Senator John F. Kennedy speaks at the Biltmore Hotel during 1960 Democratic Convention in Los Angeles, CA July 1960 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., ca. 1955-1965. (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Black and white shots of Kennedy throughout political career. Includes shots of wife Ethel, at Democratic Convention, with family, and with brother John.
    - Attorney General Robert F. Kennedy in his office ca. 1963 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Senator Robert Kennedy ca. 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Elizabeth, Queen Mother, consort of George VI, King of Great Britain, 1900-2002, ca. 1952. (Box 6, Folder 32)
    2.5 x 2.5" black and white shots of the Queen Mother speaking and greeting crowd.